Hello everyone, I am a former volunteer artist, Wu Wennan, but people who are familiar with me usually call me Xiaoqianbao, and people online call me this name.
Today, I would like to share with you the theme of this video, which is the invisible standard of real-time material writing.
Before that, I would like to introduce myself briefly.
I have been working on real-time 3D games for about 11 years.
I have participated in the production of Destiny 2, Summoner of the Deceased, Dying Line, Hunter Hunter, and other 3D games.
In recent years, I have been working on clothing.
I am good at making super real-time clothing.
Today, I would like to talk about four parts of this topic.
The first one.
The second one.
What is the invisible standard?
What is clothing engineering?
And what can MD be used for?
And the last one.
A simple analysis of the bag.
The standard.
What is the standard?
Since the beginning of the 2000s, the current game has been around 2000 years old.
The development of domestic games has been around 25 years.
At the beginning, it was the era of mobile games.
At that time, it was the era of mobile games.
For example, Grandia, Mario 3, and New Year's Eve.
Then, around 2005, the hair line and highlights began to be applied to the game.
Then, the familiar 4-character character, the perfect world, and the real-time machine.
Then, in 2011, the PVR process began to appear.
The most familiar one is the WDW2 graphics card player.
Then, the video exchange and high-end war.
And then, the art industrialization of PVR,
WEDW3, and the power lock are created by the art industrialization.
Then, the time-lapse is what we are familiar with.
Most 3D games now are timetabled games.
Controls the sound of the dead.
Three lessons.
Then the age of A.I. support.
Then, the age of A.I. support.
The development of the game industry and the technological advancement of software
has given the entire game industry a lot of possibilities,
and at the same time, it has brought even higher requirements.
This is the initial progress of the platform.
About 10 years ago, I was looking for a...
I remember it was QQQtion.
It's the same kind of commercialized assets.
10 years ago, our needs only needed to be like this.
But 10 years later, our commercialized games need to be like this.
The one on the right is the project I was involved in before.
Whether it's our development and production,
game production, or players,
the needs are completely different from what they were a few years ago.
So the needs are the first driving force to push and improve.
In addition to the game industry,
other industries have never stopped exploring the art of design.
Here are some examples of other industries.
Clothes, products, home decor, buildings, packaging.
10 years ago, it was like this.
The design was in a relatively early stage.
Then, after more than 20 years of development,
it developed into what it is now.
No matter which industry it is,
it's all about cross-referencing.
From the decoration to the people.
The progress of cross-referencing art
is constantly reversing our game design.
Because I'm a game designer.
So no matter what the game is,
it can't escape reality.
Whether it's ancient or modern,
or science fiction,
it's all about designing based on reality.
So the development of other industries
is also gradually affecting the game industry.
I'm going to use a simple example here.
10 years ago,
most of the clothes we wore at that time
were straight-line embroideries.
Straight-line embroideries,
in the pointy part of the shoulder.
They were all straight-line embroideries.
Later on,
the Korean and Japanese trends
were introduced.
The Korean military was introduced.
Then, the cross-referencing,
the low-referencing,
these styles of clothes
gradually entered our daily lives.
Then, later on,
the development of the clothes
led to the development of the year-end embroideries.
Actually, it wasn't developed.
Actually, these embroideries
existed long ago.
But during this period,
they started to become popular in China.
Then,
straight-line embroideries,
bat-like embroideries,
bubble-like embroideries,
and sheep-like embroideries
were introduced.
Then,
a new era of the Korean War began.
There are actually many types of embroideries.
There are hundreds of them.
I just listed some of them.
Only one type of embroidery
has developed so many changes
in the short period of 20 years.
The changes in the entire clothing
in the past 20 years
can be thought of as
a huge change.
The development of other industries
led to the professionalism of the game
to improve even more.
This is the second stage of the threshold.
What technical changes
did the threshold bring?
At the beginning,
when I entered the Korean War,
I entered the Korean War
at the end of 2013.
At that time,
in order to make
a more practical costume,
a super practical one,
we had to go through
a lot of trials and tribulations.
In order to make
a more practical costume,
we had to go through
a lot of trials and tribulations.
At that time,
we had to carve
all kinds of things
with ZB.
It was very difficult
to carve with ZB.
If the design was a little bit
worse,
the difficulty
would have been
a little bit lower.
But if we were to make
the kind of sculpture
that requires
3D scanning
it would be
very difficult.
Later,
in order to reduce
this difficulty,
in the middle of 2010,
the 3D scanning technology
began to appear
and was widely used
in the game
and the film industry.
However,
in order to reduce
this difficulty,
the 3D scanning technology
began to appear.
However,
with the development
of commercialization,
the 3D scanning
limitation
began to emerge.
The 3D scanning limitation
was very large.
The large amount
of commercialization
in the later period
led to the 3D scanning
actually
not being able
to meet the needs.
Then,
the next virtual reality
appeared.
In 2009,
3D was established.
Until 2012,
MD began to promote
the entire
game industry
and film industry.
Until
before 2020,
the entire
game industry
was mainly
a bit more
realistic.
Whether it's
the ancient
or modern
style
or the overseas
or domestic
style,
it basically
requires the use
of the 1st virtual reality.
So,
the entire
1st virtual reality
process
has been gradually replaced
with the traditional
sculpting process.
When the 1st virtual reality
started to be
completely replaced
with the traditional
sculpting process,
the new threshold
began to be created.
Now,
we need
to move
the real
things
from the
platform
to the engine.
So,
the new threshold
has started to form again.
The new threshold
is the
fashion engineering.
What does
the fashion engineering
include?
The fashion engineering
is simply
a combination
of paper,
materials,
human engineering
and art design.
However,
it is
much more complex
than
the examples
we have seen
in the past.
It involves
the fashion industry
from fashion design
to fashion production
to fashion sales,
including
the whole
fashion industry.
I have listed
about
4 core elements
here.
However,
this is not
related
to our
game production.
I have listed
these 3 elements
which are
closely related
to the production
of game character
models.
The basic
technology,
fashion design
and clothing materials.
The basic
technology
is the
2D
board.
Many
people who
have used
the 2D
board for the
first time
may not
know what
the board
is.
The board
is the
ideal
way of
modeling.
The model
is to make
a 3D
module,
then cut
the UV
which is
the 2D
module.
This way,
you can easily
understand the
principle of
the 3D board.
Then,
fashion design.
Fashion design
means that
I have a
cloud function.
This is the
expansion line.
If you want
to use
the expansion line
in MD,
you need to
open the expansion line function
to see the
black edge.
Why do I
put it in
the fashion design
section?
When I
was making
fashion design
in the early days,
I used
the
expansion line function
to show
the
structure of
clothing.
You can adjust
the color
and thickness
of the line.
No matter
where you
cut,
it can be
shown.
It is also
better to
show the
expansion line
of the
inner line.
Sometimes,
we don't need
to cut
all the
clothing
at the
same time.
So,
the
expansion line
of the
fashion design
is the
symbol of
the
expansion line.
The
clothing material
is easy to
understand.
It is
not
clear.
I think
it is
physical property.
Physical property
is
perfectly
compatible
with
the
material
in
reality.
This is the
foundation of
the
fashion design.
This is
the most basic
part of
the
fashion design.
What is
the
expansion line?
I have
mentioned
the
shape
of
the
clothing.
What is
the shape
of the
clothing?
The shape
is
the
foundation
of
the
clothing.
Another
thing is
how can
we
understand
the
shape of
clothing?
For example,
the shape of
the
cloth
has
two
parts.
It can
be
the
shape of
cloth.
The shape of
the
fabric
includes
a
lot
of
patterns.
It is
the
This is one of the key points in MD, a technical point.
In clothing, it is also called Shen.
In MD, it is also called Shen.
The role of Shen is to make the clothing stick to the body more.
For men and women, there is no Shen.
There is only one Shen.
For women, there are three Shens.
This is a figure of a female figure in Japanese culture.
Next.
In this picture, I gave five examples.
In this picture, there is a Shen and Shen Dao transformation.
The following five 2D models have a very big difference.
The first one on the left is a female figure.
The second one has two male figures in a such pattern.
But through Shen transformation technology, I can cast the Shen Dao.
Shen Dao is the black line above the lead figure.
This red line is very common in modified games.
Often drawing periscope.
You may draw a knife on wearing clothes,
Or playback a jump suit.
So there are many Shen Dao for women.
Four times for men.
Then many people go to work.
What is the actual function of this line?
There is often a line that ends like this.
Or you can just cut the line and that's it.
But we don't know what the actual function of the line is.
By turning the line to different places,
I can get these lines in different places.
The line can be transferred to
any place on the fabric or on the board.
Even if the 2D board changes a lot in the 2D model,
in the 3D model,
there is almost no change in the outline.
This is the Shendao transfer.
The opposite of the Shendao transfer,
the clothing supply technology,
is the fold.
It is also based on embroidery.
The fold is made by extension.
On the right side,
I made a fold.
The 2D model is also very different from the 2D version.
I didn't put it on the side.
But if you look at the sleeves from the side,
there is not much change in the outline.
The fold and the Shendao transfer
are important parts of the clothing.
It is called the fold.
Shendao and fold are two sides of the clothing.
Shendao is the fold.
Fold is the fold.
These two things,
if you use them well,
they can help you a lot
in your whole character clothing.
Shendao is very powerful.
About the basic of the31-fold.
Because I politely changed the background color to white,
it can only do Mr. Olmas's effort.
Generally,
the fashion of Japanese fashion clothes
is based on a very complex dietetitian's brain.
The basic of the Sophie is generally스트
Some people may encounter this problem when making pants.
The waist of the pants cannot be easily combined with the body.
This part is turned over.
In this case, it is also related to the fashion design.
About the principle of fashion design, you can search it yourself.
What can I do with MD?
The first thing is daily clothing.
These are some of the exercises I made at the same time.
Skirt, jeans, T-shirt, jacket, and a t-shirt.
These are also the most common daily clothes used by MD.
In addition, I also like to make shoes with MD.
The first one is Balenciaga shoes.
I posted it on the Internet.
Many people have seen it.
The second one is Saichou's shoes.
I made a Balenciaga shoe before.
These are also made in MD.
In fact, it is not very effective to make shoes with a hard fabric.
This can be done in other three-dimensional films.
MD is more suitable for making this kind of folding,
for example, long-sleeved shoes.
For example, high-waisted shoes.
This kind of fabric is softer.
It can produce a better rhythm.
This is more effective.
In addition, it can also be used to make toys.
Something that is more loose.
There are many kinds of inflatable things in it.
The effect made by MD is also very good.
I just put four examples here.
In addition, I also like to make some kind of steel models.
Some small operations in this MD.
This MD is actually much more than we imagine.
In general, the accessories on my clothes
will actually use MD for physical calculation.
It is heavy.
In this way, it can very well
show the weight of the steel part.
Of course, it can also be used to make a steel model with
Mya, Max or Blender.
In general, I make this kind of chain
just for demonstration.
But if you really want to make this chain,
you can only make one bag.
By making a bag, the weight of the bag
represents the weight of the whole chain.
Then we go to the 3D software
to extract the path.
By extracting the path,
you can make the whole chain.
Whether you want to make a chain
or you want to make other kinds of steel models,
you can make it in this way.
Then this kind of bag
is also what I just finished in you.
In fact, MD can also make this kind of
natural surface things.
But it can only make some
slightly simpler ones.
Then this is something I made recently.
Backpack.
I have been making backpacks lately.
Single shoulder cross bag,
single day cloth bag,
multi-day cloth bag.
MD makes this kind of
backpacks.
Backpack packaging is very good.
It is much more convenient
and realistic than what we make
by hand.
Next, I will use this multi-day cloth bag
as a
case analysis
to give you a brief explanation.
The whole case analysis is
a preliminary introduction,
a design idea,
and a production idea.
The main thing is
to make this model
by understanding the designer
of a real product.
Then through
the functional and structural
expansion of the real product,
we will be able to make it.
This is what I made
in MD.
I made some details
when I was working on it.
This is what I made in MD.
This is the design for the backpack.
The parts are not part of the backpack.
I placed the top of the backpack
in the upper part of the backpack.
We'll be using this backpack
This is a video I recorded.
This backpack is basically a reality of the One-to-One Restoration.
I have used many different types of backpack to design the combination.
Thank you.
除了这些一表面的部分,除了这些一表面的部分是导入进去的,其他的都是版本制作。
这是在建立到我们手里的,但是在制作中还没有完成。
这个位置比较卡困,所以最后也摄影会比较为卡。
因为我制作的模型的面图相对来说都饰的比较高。
Thank you.
.
I have listed a few pictures here, one is an empty bag, 0% packing density, 45% packing density, 75% packing density, and 100% packing density.
Why do I want to list these pictures?
When I make a backpack and look for a reference picture, I usually look for a reference picture like this.
But when I made it, I found that the shape of the backpack was very strange.
This bag did not hold the most, it only held about 45%.
The more the backpack is held, the more flat the fold will be.
The more the backpack is held, the more the fold will be, and the deeper the fold will be.
Generally, I will look for a backpack that holds 100% of the bag and look at its cut.
Such a backpack is easy to look at the cut.
The same goes for clothing.
When I look for a reference picture of clothing, it is also best to look for a screen.
If I can't find a screen, I will look for a normal model stand.
In this way, it is easy to reverse its cut.
After the cut is done, we will make the whole body detail.
Then different packing density.
The final shape of the model presented at the end.
It is completely different.
Some people look for a reference picture like this.
It is filled with white paper.
It will be done in this way at the end.
So the final product will be very strange.
It will only have a cover.
This time, I will give some functional points of the backpack design.
The strap is made of stainless steel.
Then, the back pocket.
Then, the side pocket.
And the back pocket.
Besides.
There is a net pocket here.
I love to...
I like to apply all the colors and materials
to MD.
But normally, the materials in MD are not the correct ones.
I have the changing process in JB.
I found a color that I like the most.
I divided the outline of the backpack into two parts.
The shoulder area and the body part.
The shoulder area is the red part,
and the body part is the blue part.
The left part is a backpack with some problems.
The shoulder area is too high,
which leads to a loss of the overall width.
I put a belt under the backpack,
which reduces the loss of the overall width of the backpack.
You can move the shoulder area down.
The loss of the backpack will be better.
It will be much better than the width.
In this case,
you can make the backpack slightly slender.
The shoulder area is slightly shortened,
which leads to a twist like this.
The backpack is slightly slender,
which leads to a sense of weight.
In fact, these products can not only be produced in MDL,
but also in JB.
In fact, it is the same.
As long as there is a slight adjustment,
you can adjust the initial bad proportion
to a state with a sense of weight.
This is the way to create a backpack.
My whole work can be made from the previous page.
It starts with this ratio.
Then the design of the model.
When you first get these,
for example, when you find the tools.
It may be very complicated.
And when you design it yourself.
Or when you get the original.
It's very complicated.
Sometimes I don't know how to make it.
The simplest way is to do it like the creator.
This is the simplest way to do it.
In fact, the backpacks are in different shapes.
First, we need to shape the backpacks.
After shaping the backpacks, we can quickly use simple shapes to make the original backpacks.
These backpacks are the original.
Then, we can use this method to make the entire backpacks.
After making the entire backpacks, we can start making the materials.
When I was looking for reference materials, I thought about what kind of material I want to make.
I need to make the material to be of a high quality.
When I was making the backpacks, I thought that even without any stickers,
I could make a very good judgment of the material of the clothing by making the backpacks.
Then, we need to cut the backpacks in a clear and precise way.
Through different methods,
the backpacks are actually one of the ways to make a clear and precise judgment of the direction of the force.
By using different bandages,
we can make the backpacks heavier.
Then, we can use the side bandages to make the direction of the force more clear.
In this way, we can greatly enhance the sense of reality of the clothing.
The process of making the backpacks is quite simple.
We only need to cut three or four sides of the backpacks.
This is the backpacks I used in the previous video.
We can adjust the backpacks at the beginning of the video,
or at the end of the video.
In this video, I like to make the backpacks in a very delicate way.
You may not be able to see the backpacks in this video.
Then, I will talk about the relationship between the backpacks,
the fabric of the backpacks, and the fabric of the backpacks.
I like to adjust the layers of the backpacks.
I like to adjust the layers of the backpacks in this video.
This is a glue-paste fabric.
The main function is waterproofing.
The glue-paste fabric is made of small particles.
The fabric of the backpacks is made of small particles.
I like to adjust the details in this video.
I also like to adjust the structure of the fabric.
For example, how the backpacks are pasted,
and the relationship between the fabric and the fabric of the backpacks.
Finally, I will talk about the accessories.
This is related to the fabric.
I like to make these accessories more delicate.
These are some accessories I made in the plastic shop.
The one on the right is this one.
If the accessories are not made delicately enough,
the fabric will be less visible.
This is all I want to share with you today.
Thank you.
If you have any questions,
please ask them in the Q&A box.
Thank you.
Hello.
I would like to ask you about the tatsächlich
material & physical selection of the fabric.
The parameters of the fabric are relatively common
and the volume of the fabric is also quite large.
The volume of the fabric is also quite large,
which may not have the same effect at the same time.
When we adjust the fabric,
it may result in the same result
with different parameters from A to D.
When you are making the fabric,
What are the best and most honest conclusions about the parameters?
What are the parameters that will make the best results?
And which parameters need to be adjusted?
Usually, when I make these costumes,
I have been making costumes for so many years,
I have a saying that is,
MD's prediction is that you can't move, so don't move.
I try to use the prediction as much as possible.
Why do I say that?
The whole material property is not much,
just a dozen or so numbers and blocks,
but each block is interchangeable.
For example, the strength of the goldfish is divided by the strength of the diamond.
If you adjust the strength of the goldfish,
you must adjust the strength of the diamond.
These four values are basically the same.
If you adjust these four values,
and at the same time you want to make some changes in the posture,
then you can do it.
If you want to make a change,
then you have to adjust the deformation rate.
If you adjust the deformation rate,
then you must adjust the deformation strength.
If you adjust the deformation strength,
then you must adjust the bending strength.
The deformation strength and the bending strength actually have a certain interaction.
And these things are very complicated and complicated.
My method is generally to default.
I default and adjust everything first.
But in fact,
if you default,
to be honest,
it is enough to use all the methods.
You can make any kind of clothes.
You can make a modern dress,
or even a modern style dress.
You can make any kind of dress.
It's actually all useful.
On this basis,
I will slightly adjust the value.
For example,
I choose the Nylon.
Nylon should have four types.
Nylon,
Among these values, I choose the one I need, and then I will adjust the values not more than 10.
Because once it is more than 10, the material properties will be completely changed.
After adjusting this, after adjusting more than 10, you need to do as I just said, you need to fill all of them.
If you are very familiar with material properties, there is no problem.
If you are not familiar with material properties, it will be very troublesome if you fill all of them.
Of course, if you ask me where I adjust it, it will affect where.
This is not something that can be explained in one or two hours.
Here I need to talk about material properties specifically.
There are a lot of explanations about material properties on the Internet.
But in fact, most of the explanations are just to know what the use of material properties is.
Each and every little change in this is not too much.
As for material properties, I can only count it as one and a half.
Thank you, teacher.